<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tickle Maaaaan!</title>
    <link>http://tickleman.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tickle Maaaaan!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:04:22 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tickleman.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Story II</title>
      <link>http://tickleman.xyz/posts/story-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:04:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tickleman.xyz/posts/story-2/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, in a small town nestled in the heart of the forest, there lived a man known as the Tickle Man. The Tickle Man was a strange and mysterious figure, with long, spindly fingers that seemed to twitch and wriggle of their own accord. He had a wicked sense of humor and a mischievous streak a mile wide, and he loved nothing more than to sneak up on people and tickle them until they begged for mercy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story</title>
      <link>http://tickleman.xyz/posts/story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tickleman.xyz/posts/story/</guid>
      <description>The Tickle Man was a creature that no one had ever seen, but his presence was felt everywhere. His victims always reported the same thing - a tickling sensation, followed by an overwhelming sense of terror. No one knew where The Tickle Man came from, or what he wanted. Some said he was a demon, summoned from the depths of Hell to torment the living. Others claimed he was a scientist, driven mad by his own experiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origin</title>
      <link>http://tickleman.xyz/posts/origin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:03:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tickleman.xyz/posts/origin/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time there was a human person. He had to fight some bad guys because they didn&amp;rsquo;t believe in the tickle. Thereafter, the ticklemaan was born. He went around shooting people with his tickle fingers, sending them into tickle comas. Thus converting them to the almighty tickle. The end!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
